<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<DISEASESLIST>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>0</uiIndex>
		<szName>Arulcan plague</szName>
		<szFatName>|A|r|u|l|c|a|n |P|l|a|g|u|e</szFatName>
		<szDescription>This rare subtype of the plague is unique to Arulco. It can be spread by insects, direct contact,&#10;or by contaminated food. There have been several deadly outbreaks in the last decade.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>1</uiIndex>
		<szName>Typhoid</szName>
		<szFatName>|T|y|p|h|o|i|d</szFatName>
		<szDescription>Typhoid fever is a common worldwide bacterial disease transmitted by the ingestion of food or water&#10;contaminated with the feces of an infected person. Symptoms include internal bleeding, dehydration and delirium.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>2</uiIndex>
		<szName>Hepatitis A</szName>
		<szFatName>|H|e|p|a|t|i|t|i|s |A</szFatName>
		<szDescription>Hepatitis A is usually spread by eating or drinking contaminated food or water or through close contact with an&#10;infectious person. Symptoms may include nausea, vomiting, diarrhea, yellow skin, fever, and abdominal pain.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>3</uiIndex>
		<szName>Tetanus</szName>
		<szFatName>|T|e|t|a|n|u|s</szFatName>
		<szDescription>Infection with tetanus generally occurs through wound contamination and often involves a cut or deep puncture&#10;wound. As the infection progresses, muscle spasms develop in the jaw and elsewhere in the body.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>4</uiIndex>
		<szName>Tuberculosis</szName>
		<szFatName>|T|u|b|e|r|c|u|l|o|s|i|s</szFatName>
		<szDescription>Tuberculosisis a common, and in many cases fatal, infectious disease. It is spread through the air. About one in ten latent&#10;infections eventually progresses to active disease which, if left untreated, kills more than 50% of those so infected.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>5</uiIndex>
		<szName>Cholera</szName>
		<szFatName>|C|h|o|l|e|r|a</szFatName>
		<szDescription>Main symptoms of Cholera are watery diarrhea and vomiting. This may result in dehydration and in severe cases grayish-bluish skin.&#10;Transmission occurs primarily by contaminated water or food. Severe cholera can lead to death.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>6</uiIndex>
		<szName>Ebola</szName>
		<szFatName>|E|b|o|l|a</szFatName>
		<szDescription>A deadly virus with no known treatment, Ebola has a an unusually high lethality rate of over 50%%. Symptoms include nausea, vomiting,&#10;diarrhea and internal bleeding.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>7</uiIndex>
		<szName>Malaria</szName>
		<szFatName>|M|a|l|a|r|i|a</szFatName>
		<szDescription>Malaria is a mosquito-borne infectious disease commonly transmitted by a bite from an infected mosquito. Malaria &#10;causes symptoms that typically include fever and headache, which in severe cases can progress to coma or death.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>8</uiIndex>
		<szName>Staphylococcus</szName>
		<szFatName>|S|t|a|p|h|y|l|o|c|o|c|c|u|s</szFatName>
		<szDescription>A staphylococcus infection is a common result of food poisoning. Symptoms include spontaneous vomiting and diarrhea.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>	
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>9</uiIndex>
		<szName>Chlamydia</szName>
		<szFatName>|C|h|l|a|m|y|d|i|a</szFatName>
		<szDescription>Chlamydia is one of the most common sexually transmitted infections. If left untreated, chlamydial infections &#10; can cause serious reproductive and other health problems with both short-term and long-term consequences.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>10</uiIndex>
		<szName>Ballistic trauma</szName>
		<szFatName>|B|a|l|l|i|s|t|i|c |t|r|a|u|m|a</szFatName>
		<szDescription>Ballistic trauma or gunshot wound is a form of physical trauma sustained from the discharge of arms or munitions. &#10; Non-fatal gunshot wounds frequently have severe and long-lasting effects, even after the victim has made a successful recovery.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>11</uiIndex>
		<szName>PTSD</szName>
		<szFatName>|P|T|S|D</szFatName>
		<szDescription>|Post|traumatic |stress |disorder may develop after a person is exposed to one or more traumatic events, such as sexual assault,&#10;warfare, serious injury, or threats of imminent death that result in feelings of intense fear, horror, and powerlessness.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>12</uiIndex>
		<szName>Wounded leg</szName>
		<szFatName>|W|o|u|n|d|e|d |l|e|g</szFatName>
		<szDescription>The human musculoskeletal system is complicated. Your leg received a critical wound, and while it heals, your mobility is affected.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>13</uiIndex>
		<szName>Damaged arm</szName>
		<szFatName>|D|a|m|a|g|e|d |a|r|m</szFatName>
		<szDescription>You were shot in the arm. Apart from being very painful, this severely limits your motor abilities.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>14</uiIndex>
		<szName>Wounded biceps</szName>
		<szFatName>|W|o|u|n|d|e|d |b|i|c|e|p|s</szFatName>
		<szDescription>A painful shot to your torso has you gasping for air. You'll have to cut back in the next days. </szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>15</uiIndex>
		<szName>Drug Addiction</szName>
		<szFatName>|D|r|u|g |A|d|d|i|c|t|i|o|n</szFatName>
		<szDescription>You've become addicted to various substances. Until your body has removed all traces of drugs, you will suffer from withdrawal.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<uiIndex>16</uiIndex>
		<szName>Hungover</szName>
		<szFatName>|H|u|n|g|o|v|e|r</szFatName>
		<szDescription>That last beer was definitely spoiled.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
	<DISEASE>
		<!-- As cancer grows over a long time, it does not grow on itself ingame, only by consuming cigarettes -->
		<uiIndex>17</uiIndex>
		<szName>Lung Cancer</szName>
		<szFatName>|L|u|n|g |C|a|n|c|e|r</szFatName>
		<szDescription>Lung cancer is a malignant lung tumor characterized by uncontrolled cell growth in tissues of the lung. If left untreated, this growth can spread beyond the lung.</szDescription>
	</DISEASE>
</DISEASESLIST>
